https://www.sportomotoring.com/privacy-policy

You Are Now Subscribed
Sporto Motoring Accessories | Automotive Information of Interest
Privacy Policy
Sporto Motoring is committed to protecting your privacy. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Sporto Motoring website and governs data collection and usage. By using the Sporto Motoring website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
Sporto Motoring collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home and or work address and or telephone number. Sporto Motoring also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.
There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Sporto Motoring. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used by Sporto Motoring for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Sporto Motoring website.
In the event that you contact us for customer support through the website, we may also request that you provide additional User Information relevant to the support requested by you. Users are under no obligation to provide such information. However, we cannot guarantee that we can provide customer support in the event that relevant information related to the use of our products or services is withheld. We may retain communications relating to customer support, and/or information drawn from such communications, for statistical and/or reference purposes.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Sporto Motoring public message boards or forums, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: Sporto Motoring does not read your private online communications with others.
Sporto Motoring encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Sporto Motoring so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Sporto Motoring is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Sporto Motoring and Sporto Motoring family of websites or the use of your information by such outside websites.
Use of your Personal Information
Sporto Motoring collects and uses your personal information to operate the Sporto Motoring website and deliver the services you have requested. Sporto Motoring may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Sporto Motoring and its affiliates. Sporto Motoring may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services.
Sporto Motoring does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Sporto Motoring may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Sporto Motoring may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. Such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Sporto Motoring and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
Sporto Motoring does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.
Sporto Motoring keeps track of the websites and pages you visit within Sporto Motoring, in order to determine what Sporto Motoring services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Sporto Motoring to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
Sporto Motoring websites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Sporto Motoring or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Sporto Motoring (including enforcing this agreement); and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Sporto Motoring, or the public.
Use of Cookies
The Sporto Motoring website use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies are not used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Sporto Motoring pages, or register with Sporto Motoring site or services, a cookie helps Sporto Motoring to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Sporto Motoring website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Sporto Motoring features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Sporto Motoring services or websites you visit.
If you provide Sporto Motoring with user information, you have the following rights with respect to that information:
To review the user information that you have supplied to us
To request that we correct any errors, outdated information, or omissions in user information that you have supplied to us
To request that your user information not be used to contact you
To request that your user information be removed from any solicitation list that we use
To request that your user information be deleted from our records and
To opt out of being solicited by this website or third parties
If you request that your user information be deleted from our records, there may be a brief delay in our processing that request, while verify that the request is valid and originates from you as opposed to an unauthorized third party. If you request that your information be deleted, we reserve the right to terminate and or limit your access to the Sporto Motoring website.
To exercise any of these rights, please contact us at Sporto@SportoMotoring.com.
Security of your Personal Information
No method of safeguarding information is 100% secure. Sporto Motoring uses a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Sporto Motoring secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
Changes to this Statement
Sporto Motoring will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Sporto Motoring encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Sporto Motoring is protecting your information. When such a change is made, we will update the “Last Updated” date above.
Enforcement of this Privacy Statement
If you have questions regarding this statement, you should contact us at Sporto@SportoMotoring,com.
Contact Information
Sporto Motoring welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Sporto Motoring has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Sporto Motoring at Sporto@SportoMotoring.com. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem
Hey Look – A Tweet Button! This probably increases your Klout score.
Tweet
You can follow us too:
Follow @SportoMotoring
Sporto Motoring on facebook
Now you can tell all your "friends" about this page or post!
We Are Cornhole
News & Reviews
Articles (112)
Automotive Store (1)
Editorial (20)
Industry News (6)
Info Article (4)
News (89)
Previous Publications (26)
Reviews (21)
Subscribe Now!
Testimonial
Sporto Motoring Disclosure From. time to time, this website may include links to sponsors and recommended resources from which Sporto Motoring may receive compensation.
Recommendations are based on their merit. No advertiser will influence the content on this website.
News & Reviews
Articles (112)
Automotive Store (1)
Editorial (20)
Industry News (6)
Info Article (4)
News (89)
Previous Publications (26)
Reviews (21)
Sporto Motoring Accessories | Automotive Information of Interest
Suv Pet Products Outlet Cincinnati OH
Suv Seat Covers Dealer Cincinnati OH
Truck Accessories Store Cincinnati OH
©
2020 Best Automotive News & Reviews. WordPress Theme by Solostream.
